dlink.com.vn 2017-12-23

# Privacy Policy - D-Link Vietnam

D-Link Systems, Inc. (“we” or “us”) is committed to providing you with a positive, easy and secure online shopping experience.

D-Link Systems, Inc. (USA) manages [www.dlink.com](http://www.dlink.com/)

Our Policy explained:

1\. What information is collected?  
2\. What do we use the information for?  
3\. Sharing of information  
4\. Use of Cookies  
5\. Policy changes

**1\. What information is collected?**

Any information you enter during the submission of forms or an order on D-Link Systems, Inc. can be collected and stored in our customer database. In order to better define the types of information that is collected, D-Link Systems, Inc. has identified and grouped these into two categories:  
a) Personal Information; and  
b) General Non-Specific & Demographic Information.

**Personal Information  
**Personal information as defined by this Privacy Policy is any information that identifies you personally, such as name, address, telephone number and email address.

**General Non-Specific & Demographic Information  
**Any non-personal information either entered by you or recorded as part of the transaction process is considered to be General Non-Specific & Demographic Information. This is information that does not contain personal information, rather is comprised of the type and quantities of products purchased, and any demographic information.

D-Link Systems, Inc. also has the ability to track your navigation through this site by recording the Uniform Resource Locator (URL), as well as your computer’s IP address, which is a unique address assigned to your PC by your Internet Service Provider or Information Systems Department on a TCP/IP network.

**2\. What do we use the information for?**

In order to provide you with the best online experience possible, we collect both personal and non-personal information to give us a better understanding of the demographic and geographic profile of our customers. The information we collect is reviewed closely to assist us in determining the most popular products of interest to our customers, and better structure our site(s) to suit your needs.

By tracking your IP through our site, we can better understand the types of products and information which is relevant to our customers and may from time to time, use this information to provide our customers with information or promotions which match their various geo- and demographic dynamics.

From time to time, we may send surveys to our customers via email or online at our website in order to solicit your feedback on improvements we should make to the site in order to improve your online experience. These surveys are completed on a voluntary basis and personal and general information are not required. Refusal to complete the survey or poll will not result in any penalization of the customer(s) standings with our organization. Should you not wish to receive notification of subsequent surveys or polls, you can click the link supplied at the bottom of every promotional e-mail we send you to request that you not receive such notifications in the future.

We may also run contests and/or sweepstakes at various times. By entering the sweepstakes you agree to disclose your personal information for our use in future marketing campaigns. Your consent for our use of your information is a condition of your participation and eligibility for any such contest or sweepstakes.

Should you contact us via the email contact links on our site, or via telephone or written correspondence, we may keep your comments on file for future use in our contact database.

**3\. Sharing of Information**

The primary purpose of collecting personal and non-personal information on this site is for the purposes of informing you of ongoing marketing activities to keep you apprised of new products, special offers or contests we may run from time to time.

Your personal information will not be sold, traded or rented to another party and is for the express internal use of D-Link Systems, Inc. and D-Link Systems, Inc. only except as otherwise stated in this policy.

**4\. Use of Cookies**

“Cookies” are files that are created by websites and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a website or information that allows us to customise our websites for your use. A D-Link cookie cannot be recognized or viewed by another website, thus ensuring privacy on the customers’ or web visitors’ part. There is no way for a cookie to view or store any information from your hard drive, capture your email address, or pass on a computer virus.

D-Link or a third party acting on our behalf may use cookies to tailor and improve the content we deliver to our web visitors, to improve our websites by assessing which areas, features, and products are most popular, and to personalize our websites and make recommendations based on information, including product choices, a particular visitor has previously provided. We may also use cookies to store user preferences, complete online order activity, and keep track of transactions.

D-Link uses cookies for the following specific purposes:

  * To remember whether the Home, Business or Service Provider section of the D-Link website is your preferred area;
  * To remember if you have downloaded a Latest Resource document on the Business homepage;
  * To gather analytics and usage data (with the ultimate aim of improving the experience for our users);
  * To remember your basket contents (US D-Link site only)

You can configure your web browser to alert you when a website is attempting to send a cookie to your computer and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer, including third party cookies, or delete cookies previously accepted, by adjusting your web browser preferences. Some web pages may not work correctly if you have cookies disabled.

**How to enable and disable cookies using your browser**

If you do disable our cookies you may find that certain sections of our website do not function properly.

**a. Google Chrome**

  * Click on the ‘wrench’ icon on the browser (usually found top-right corner) to open the tools menu
  * From the tools menu select ‘Options’
  * Click the ‘Under the Hood’ tab from the menu on the left.
  * In the ‘Privacy’ section, select the ‘Content settings’ button
  * To enable cookies: select ‘Allow local data to be set’ option
  * To disable cookies: select ‘Block all cookies’ option

Note there are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Chrome. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Chrome, refer to the following page from Google: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

**b. Microsoft Internet Explorer**

  * Click on ‘Tools’ at the top of your browser window and select ‘Internet Options’
  * In the options window navigate to the ‘Privacy’ tab
  * To enable cookies: Set the slider to ‘Medium’ or below
  * To disable cookies: Move the slider to the top to block all cookies

Note there are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Explorer. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Internet Explorer, refer to the following page from Microsoft: [http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies)

**c. Mozilla Firefox**

  * Click on ‘Tools’ at the browser menu and select ‘Options’
  * Select the Privacy panel
  * To enable cookies: Check ‘Accept cookies for sites’
  * To disable cookies: Uncheck at ‘Accept cookies for sites’

Note there are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Firefox. For more information, refer to the following page from Mozilla: [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies)

**d. Opera**

  * Click on ‘Setting’ at the browser menu and select ‘Settings’
  * Select ‘Quick Preferences’
  * To enable cookies: check “Enable Cookies”
  * To disable cookies: uncheck “Enable Cookies”

Note there are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Opera. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Opera, refer to the following page from Opera Software:[http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/](http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/)

**e. Safari on OSX**

  * Click on ‘Safari’ at the menu bar and select the ‘Preferences’ option
  * Click on ‘Security’
  * To enable cookies: In the ‘Accept cookies’ section select ‘Only from site you navigate to’
  * To disable cookies: In the ‘Accept cookies’ section select ‘Never’

Note there are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Safari. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Safari, refer to the following page from Apple:  
[http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/3.0/en/9277.html](http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/3.0/en/9277.html)

**f. All other browsers**

  * Please look for a “help” function in the browser or contact the browser provider

**5\. Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy has been developed and implemented in accordance with the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, which came into effect January 1, 2001. As changes to our information gathering practices change, we will update this policy as required. Information contained in this policy may change at any time without notice, so please be sure to check our Privacy Policy statement regularly before disclosing any personal or non-personal information through this website.
